(Bernadette:)That's such good news, Howie.
Thank you for telling her.
(Howard:)Hey, I'm a grown man.
I'm gonna live with my wife.
(Howard:)My mother's just gonna have to learn
to make do on her own.
(Bernadette:)Was she upset?
(Howard:)Who can tell? She yells everything.
(Howard:)She might have been upset.
(Howard:)She might have been hungry.
(Bernadette:)Thanks for fixing it. I love you.
(Howard:)I love you too. Sweet dreams.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Goodnight, Rocket Man.
(Howard:)To infinity and beyond, baby.
(Dimitri:)Loops, you realize you just lied your ass off
to your wife and your mother.
(Howard:)- I know.
- What are you gonna do when you get back?
Oh, I'm never going back. Heh.